Contact

trobertsjackson@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ tashiana-jackson-phd-c-rn-bccmsrn-991957135 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Clinical Research
Leadership Development

Tashiana Jackson PhD(c), RN-BC, CMSRN

Nursing Professional Development Specialist, Executive Nursing Practice Group

Pearland, Texas

Summary

Experienced Clinical Nurse Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Clinical Research, Nursing Education, and Acute Care Management. Outgoing educated professional currently pursuing a Doctor of Philosophy (PhD) degree focused in Nursing Science from The University of Texas.

Experience

Harris Health System
4 years 10 months

Nursing Professional Development Specialist September 2019 - Present (10 months)

Clinical Nurse Educator October 2016 - September 2019 (3 years)

Nursing Manager September 2015 - October 2016 (1 year 2 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Doctor of Philosophy (PhD), Nursing Science (2016 - 2020)